robertsspaceindustries.com 2013-10-17

# Privacy Policy - Roberts Space Industries

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. WHEN YOU USE ANY ONLINE GAME, SERVICE or WEBSITE FROM CLOUD IMPERIUM GAMES CORPORATION, ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR AFFILIATES (“CLOUD IMPERIUM”) YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS.**

**Cloud Imperium respects your privacy and understands the importance of protecting your personal information. We will only collect information we need to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. We will never send you marketing communications without your consent, and we will never share your personal information with third parties that are not bound by our privacy policy unless you tell us we can.**

By registering for a Cloud Imperium Account, we may transfer and store your account information. By registering, you agree that Cloud Imperium may process your data in accordance with the following privacy policy and that you will abide by Cloud Imperium’s Terms of Service.

BY REGISTERING FOR A CLOUD IMPERIUM ACCOUNT, USING THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE CLOUD IMPERIUM ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE ANY CLOUD IMPERIUM SITE, ONLINE PRODUCT OR SERVICE. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, the home page or other places so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material or significant changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email and/or by a notice at [www.robertsspaceindustries.com/privacy](http://robertsspaceindustries.com/privacy) and/or during log in. Revisions to terms affecting existing Cloud Imperium Services shall be effective thirty (30) days after posting. Your continued use of our online and mobile products and services will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Policy.  

Cloud Imperium respects the privacy rights of consumers and recognizes the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted this global Privacy Policy to explain how we store and use personal and non-personal information we collect online on our websites, during your use of our website, online products and/or services (including online game play).

Cloud Imperium collects both personal and non-personal consumer information. Personal information collected by Cloud Imperium is discussed below in this section. Non-personal information is discussed below in Section III.

### A. Personal Information Collected By Cloud Imperium

Personal information is information that identifies you and that may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. Cloud Imperium may collect personal information from our online visitors during registration and use of our website and online products.  
Cloud Imperium also may maintain log files which contain IP addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that may be assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. In general, we use log files to monitor traffic on our websites and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of user abuse of our websites, however, we may block certain IP addresses. If available, IP addresses and console IDs may be used to personally identify you in order to enforce our Terms of Service.

### B. Personal Information Provided To Cloud Imperium By Third Parties.

We may also receive other personal information from third parties in connection with the operation and distribution of our website and online products as well as market and demographic studies that we use to supplement personal information provided directly by you. As with all other information, we use this data only for purposes consistent with this policy.

Non-personal information, alone, cannot be used to identify or contact you. Cloud Imperium collects non-personal information about your use of our website and online products.

### A. What Types of Non-Personal Information Does Cloud Imperium Collect?

When you use Cloud Imperium website and online products, we may collect certain non-personal demographic information including gender, zip code, information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, media, mobile device. We also collect other non-personal information such as feature usage, game play statistics and scores, user rankings and click paths as well as other data that you may provide in surveys, via your account preferences and online profiles or through purchases, for instance. We may also receive either non-personal or public information from third parties in connection with market and demographic studies that we use to supplement personal information provided directly by you.

### B. How Does Cloud Imperium Collect Non-Personal Information?

Cloud Imperium collects non-personal information in addition to personal information when you actively provide it in the context of various online activities including online polls and marketing surveys, for instance. In addition, we might use cookies and other technologies to passively collect non-personal demographic information, personalize your experience on our sites.

1\. Cookies  
Cookies are small files applied to your Internet browser to track movements within websites. We may link cookie information to personal information. Cookies link to information regarding what items you have viewed. Also, we may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and to monitor website or game usage. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent.  
We may also use flash cookies, also known as “local shared objects,” on our sites that employ Flash technology. Flash cookies are small files similar to browser cookies and are used to remember the site’s settings to personalize the look and feel of the site. Flash cookies only collect data in the aggregate. Like normal cookies, Flash cookies are represented as small files on your computer.  
Please note that this privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Cloud Imperium only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

2\. Analytic Metrics Tool And Other Technologies  
Cloud Imperium may also use its own proprietary analytic metrics tool and other analytics technologies to collect non-personal information when you use our online products and services.  

## IV. What Happens To The Information Cloud Imperium Collects?

### A. How Cloud Imperium Uses Your Information

Cloud Imperium uses your information to operate Cloud Imperium’s website, fulfill your specific requests, and to send you account-related information. In addition, if you choose to receive communications from us about Cloud Imperium products and news, the personal information you provide will allow us to send you messages about things including new features, enhancements, contests and events of interest. You may also later opt out of this service from Cloud Imperium.

### B. Will Cloud Imperium Share My Information With Third Parties?

Cloud Imperium will never share your personal information with third parties without your consent. We may, however, share non-personal data in the aggregate (in a form that does not personally identify you) with third parties. You may also opt in to allow Cloud Imperium to share your personal information with companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.  
From time to time, Cloud Imperium may employ third party contractors to collect personal information on our behalf to provide email delivery, product, or promotional fulfillment, contest administration, credit card processing, shipping or other services on our sites. When requesting these services, you may be asked to supply your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address to our contractors. We ask some third party contractors, such as credit agencies or market research firms, to supplement personal information that you provide to us for our own marketing and demographic studies, so that we can consistently improve our sites and to better meet our visitors’ needs and preferences.  
When our third party contractors collect and/or have access to the personal information you provide to Cloud Imperium, Cloud Imperium requires that they adhere to our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of personal information they collect or have access to in the course of their engagement by Cloud Imperium. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose without your specific consent.  
We may also disclose personal information to law enforcement, or the appropriate civil authorities to enforce legal rights and comply with the law, or to comply with an order from a government entity or other competent authority, or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary to address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property, operations, users or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or damage, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, combat fraud and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Cloud Imperium.

Cloud Imperium utilizes data storage facilities located in the United States.

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards, including the guidelines developedby theOnlinePrivacy Alliance and the Federal Trade Commission to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and in storage. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, please contact us at privacy@cloudimperiumgames.com.

You can correct, update or delete your account information at any time by logging on our site and navigating to “My Account,” “View My Profile” or other account settings or contacting support@cloudimperiumgames.com. Should you be unable to log in contact at support@cloudimperiumgames.com. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our websites.

You may choose to disclose information about yourself in the course of contributing user generated content to Cloud Imperium sites or in public online chat rooms, blogs, message boards, user “profiles” for public view or in similar forums on our sites. Information that you disclose in any of these forums is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality there.  
You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit in the course of these public activities can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.  
If you post a video, image or photo on one of our sites for public view you should be aware that these may be viewed, collected, copied and/or used by other users without your consent. We are not responsible for the videos, images or photos that you choose to submit to Cloud Imperium’s site.

Our website may contain advertising or services which link to other websites such as Twitter, Facebook and YouTube. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave the Cloud Imperium site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as Cloud Imperium. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to a Cloud Imperium site, you should consult that site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information.

Members may register for other services from our site(s). Certain products and/or services available on our site are provided to you in partnership with third party(s) and may require you to disclose personally identifiable information in order to register for and access such products and/or services. Such products and/or services shall identify the third party partners at the point of registration. If you elect to register for such products and/or services your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information in connection with such products and/or services.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact the Cloud Imperium Privacy Policy Administrator at [privacy@CloudImperiumGames.com](mailto:privacy@cloudimperiumgames.com).
